&GT；&GT；凯尔·辛普森：所以他们只能走这么远。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: So they can only go so far.
它们可以告诉您我们在编译时可以告诉您的内容，但是
They can tell you what we can tell you at compile time, but
他们真的不能告诉你在现实世界里会发生什么。
they can't really tell you anything about what's gonna happen in the real world.
他们只是希望这些都不会咬到你。
They're just gonna hope that none of that bites you.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：一些打字脚本和流程的示例，以及
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: So some examples of TypeScript and Flow, and
这两个例子实际上是相同的。
these examples are actually identical between the two.
在这些情况下，它们使用相同的语法。
They use identical syntax in these cases.
有一些细微的差别。
There are a few little nuanced differences.
但实际上我在研究这项准备工作时感到非常惊讶
But I was actually remarkably surprised in my research for this preparation how
类似的打字稿和流程是在他们看起来像什么方面。
similar TypeScript and Flow are in terms of of what they look like.
我预计会有很多不同之处，但是很少，好吗？
I expected a lot of differences and there are very few, okay?
所以第一，如果你根本不打字，打字稿和
So number one, if you don't do any typing at all, both TypeScript and
默认情况下，Flow将执行一些推理。
Flow by default will do some inferencing.
所以在这里他们做了一个静态类型推断，这意味着我的意图
So here they're doing a static types inference, which means my intent that
他们在猜测，就是我想让教师，这个变量永远只包含字符串。
they're guessing, is that I want teacher, the variable to only ever hold strings.
当我稍后尝试给它分配一些非字符串的值时，
And when I later try to assign it something non-string,
它抛出一个错误，并说，你正在做一个你不应该做的作业。
it throws me an error, and says, you're doing an assignment that you shouldn't do.
这是他们最好的猜测。
That's their best guess.
有些人认为类型中最大的问题之一是我们
Some people feel that one of the biggest problems within types is that we
意外地将一个值赋给了一个不是我们所想的类型的变量。
accidentally assign a value to a variable that is not the type we thought.
因此对他们来说，静态类型是一件大事。
And so for them, static types are a big deal.
我告诉你，在我20多年的生活中，我对你说的是实话
I'm being honest with you when I tell you that in my 20 plus years in
编码从来没有一次，一次都没有错误是我偶然的结果
coding never once, not once has a bug been as a result of me accidentally
例如，将数字赋给用于保存字符串的变量。
assigning a number to a variable that used to hold a string, for example.
我经常故意这样做，但从来没有一次是偶然发生的，而且
I do that on purpose a lot, but never once has that accidentally happened, and
是一个窃听器的来源。
been the source of a bug.
所以对我来说，这不是我的问题之一。
So for me, that's not one of the problems that I have.
如果是你的问题，
If it is a problem that you have,
当错误由于重新分配错误而出现时，这是很有帮助的。
where bugs come because you've reassigned something incorrectly, this is helpful.
这是其中一个特征，在很长一段时间内，
This is one of those features that, for a long time,
我说了我不需要打字稿的那部分。
I said I don't need that part of TypeScript.
我不喜欢它向我抱怨我给变量赋值的内容，
I don't like for it to complain to me about what I assign variables,
因为我喜欢能够分配一个数字，然后再分配一个字符串。
cuz I like to be able to assign a number and then later a string.
这对我很有帮助，所以
That to me is helpful, so
我不喜欢这个部分，我觉得它是在解决一个我没有的问题。
I didn't like this part, and I felt like it was solving a problem I didn't have.
但这就是我们所说的静态类型，
But that's what we refer to as static types,
根据进入变量的值推断变量具有类型。
inferring that the variable has a type based upon the value that goes into it.
JavaScript变量没有类型，但是
JavaScript variables don't have types, but
如果你愿意，我们会对这个额外的要求进行分层，好吗？
we're layering on this extra requirement if you will, okay?
所以这就是我们不注释类型的时候，但是
So that's when we don't annotate the types, but
当然，我们可以对类型进行注释。
of course we can annotate the types.
我们可以说老师绝对是一根绳子。
We can say teacher is definitely a string.
我们将得到基本相同的错误，但这里我们不是在猜测错误。
We're gonna get basically the same error, but here we're not guessing at the error.
我们的字面意思是我想让这玩意儿永远只拿着弦，而且
We're literally saying I intended for this thing to only ever hold strings, and
现在你试图给它加上一些非字符串的东西。
now you're trying to put something non-string to it.
在这两种情况下，TypeScript和Flow都会抛出一个错误并说，
In both cases TypeScript and Flow are gonna throw us an error and say,
你在分配一些你不该做的事，好吗？
you're assigning something you shouldn't have, okay?
好极了
Great